UNITE President's Office Files 6000/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE President's Office Files
1987-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mazur, Jay
6000/010
16 cubic feet
16 linear ft.
Records.
6791859
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 28, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs
Textile industry -- New York (State); Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Mazur, Jay; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. President's Office; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6791859
- ILGWU 100th Anniversary, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Foundation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- UNITE Constitutional Convention, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- UNITE Constitutional Convention Speech, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Convention - Merger Convention, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILGWU (UNITE) - Merger - PR Campaign, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- UNITE Civil Rights Conference, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- UNITE Mid-America Leadership Training, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- UNITE Organizing Directors Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- UNITE Political and Educational Director Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- UNITE General Advisory Council, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- UNITE Major Market Negotiations, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- UNITE Appointment Agendas, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Mazur Biography, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Call Sheets, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Mazur Call Sheets, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Mazur Call Sheets, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Mazur Contact Information, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Health Center - Sanatorium Board, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- UNITE Retiree Activist Network, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- UNITE Retiree Club, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- UNITE Retiree Senior Action Committee, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Unity House Davis R. Chant Realtors, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Local 23-25, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Local 89-22-1 Agenda, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- ILGWU (UNITE) Mid-Atlantic Region, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board Conference, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- UNITE New Jersey Locals, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- UNITE NYS Membership, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- UNITE Pennsylvania, Ohio, South Jersey Joint Board Meeting at Taminent Resort in Pennsylvania, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Puerto Rican District Council, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- ILGWU Canada - Quebec Joint Council, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Retiree Health Benefits, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Health Benefit Fund, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Death Benefit Fund - Investment Performance Review, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- UNITE / ILGWU Staff Retirement, Investment Performance Review 1st Quarter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- UNITE/ILGWU Staff Retirement/Canadian Staff Retirement, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ILGWU National Retirement Fund - Investment Performance Review, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- UNITE General Fund - ILGWU Funds Performance Review 1st Quarter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- UNITE General Fund - ILGWU Funds Investment Performance Review 2nd Quarter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- UNITE General Funds - ILGWU Funds Performance Review 4th Quarter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- UNITE General Fund - ILGWU Funds Performance Review 3rd Quarter, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare Fund Performance Review 1st Quarter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Eastern States Health and Welfare 2nd Quarter, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund Executive Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund Expense Allocation Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Co-Salary + Expense Review / Allocation Working Group, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund Meeting of Banking Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company Banking Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- ARC, ALICO, AFA Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund - Retirement, Insurance + SoCal Subfund, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- CLOFUND, SoCal Subfund Investment Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- ALICO - Meeting of Investment Sub-Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- CLOFUND SoCal Subfund COTFUND Meetings of I.C. + E.C., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- CLOFUND SoCal COTFUND Investment, Executive Committee Reports, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- CLOFUND Board of Trustees Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- COTFUND Executive Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- COTFUND Investment Committee Meetings, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- COTFUND E.C. Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- COTFUND Investment Committee Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- COTFUND Board of Trustees Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- COTFUND Meetings, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- ALICO Banking Committee Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- CLOFUND Banking Committee Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- ALICO, ASC, AFA Meetings, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- ALICO Investment Sub-committee, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- SoCal CLOFUND Board of Trustees Meeting, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- CLOFUND EC + EAC Meetings, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- CLOFUNd SoCal Investment Committees, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- COTFUND Board of Trustees Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- COTFUND Executive Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- COTFUND Investment Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- COTFUND Banking Committee, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ALICO Banking Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ALICO Investment Sub-committee, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- CLOFUND Executive Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- CLOFUND, ASC, ALICO Meetings, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- CLOFUND Investment Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- CLOFUND Banking Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- SoCal Sub Fund Investment Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Africa, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- American ORT, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Brooks Brothers, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Carnegie Endowment Policy Brief, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Child Labor, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- China (Trade), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- China (Trade), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- China (Trade), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- China (Trade), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- China (Trade), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- China, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- China (Trade), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- China, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- China (Trade), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- China, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- China Lu Jinghua, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Clinton, Bill, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Clinton / Gore Campaign, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Cornell Kheel Records Management Project, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cuba, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Davos, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Davos World Economic Forum, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Delay, Tom, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Ethical Practice Code (AFL CIO), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- FIT (Fashion Institute of Technology), 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Foreign Affairs Article, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Foreign Affairs Article - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Frontlash, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Gang Meeting (Democratic Party) - Carl McCall, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Gang Meeting (Democratic Party), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Gang Meeting (Democratic Party), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Garment Industry Development Corp (GIDC), 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- (Giuliani) Political Meeting, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Globalization, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Gore, Jr., Vice President Al, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Health Care - National Coalition on Health Care, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Health Care - National Leadership Coalition on Health Care, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Health care, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Herman, Alexis, Secretary of Labor, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Hoekstra Hearings Hoekstra Hearings, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Immigrant Workers, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Immigrant Workers - INS Racial Profiling, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Immigration, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Immigration & Organization, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Immigration - International Rescue Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Immigration - Center for Immigration Studies, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Immigration, National Immigration Forum, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Indonesia Solidarity Center, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- International Labor Office (ILO), 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- ITGLWF (International Textile, Garment, and Leather Workers Federation), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Islam, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Kamberis, Harry, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Kanton, Mickey, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Labor, U.S. Department of, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Labor Day, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Labor Day, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Labor Leadership Forum - Howard / AFL-CIO, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Labor Movement, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Laundry and Dry Cleaning International Union, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Lake Research Opinion Survey, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- McCall, Carl Rally, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Media: Crain's Interview, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Media Interviews: Citizens Union, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Media Interviews - Friedman, Arthur, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Mexico - Fox Inauguration, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Mexico, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Mexico - Free Trade, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Mexico - Maquiladoras, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Minimum Wage, 1995-2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Minnesota Management Review, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- NAFTA, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- NAFTA, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- NAFTA - Fast Track, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- NAFTA, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- National Consumers' League Board, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- National Labor Committee, Haiti, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- National Planning Association - "When Earnings Diverge", 1996 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- NYC Economy - Sept. 11, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Garment Center Special District, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- NYC Councilman Hoach Dear, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- NYC - GIAC (Garment Industry Advisory Council), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Political Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Postal Workers, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Reich, Robert, Secretary of Labor, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- South Africa, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Sweatshops, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Sweatshops`, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Sweatshops - Newspaper Clippings, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Sweatshops, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Sweatshops - Stop Sweatshop Campaign, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Sweatshops, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Sweatshops - Marymount University, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Trade, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Triangle Fire Commemoration, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Triangle Fire - New Internationalism, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Triangle Fire Anniversary, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Triangle Fire Commemoration, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Triangle Fire Commemoration, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Triangle Fire Commemoration, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Trilateral Commission, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Trilateral Commission, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Trilateral Commission, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Trilateral Commission - Tokyo Meeting, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Twentieth Century Fund - Report on Future of Labor Movement, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Twentieth Century Fund - Task Force on Future of American Labor Movement, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Twentieth Century Fund - Task Force, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Twentieth Century Fund - Task Force, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- United Farm Workers of America, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- United Housing Foundation, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Wilson, Gwendolyn, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Work and Technology Institute - Reports, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Work and Technology Institute, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Work in America Institute, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Work in America Institute - Awards Ceremony, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Work in America Institute - Freeman Survey, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Work in America Institute - Productivity Forum, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Working for America Institute, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Working Together for Public Service (U.S. Dept of Labor) Report, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Workman's Circle, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- World Trade Organization, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Zensen, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Zimbabwe, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- GIAC Meeting, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Correspondence A, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Correspondence B, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Correspondence B, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Mazur - Correspondence - C, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Correspondence E, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Correspondence F, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Correspondence G, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Correspondence H, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Correspondence I, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Correspondence J, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Correspondence K, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Correspondence L, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Correspondence M, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Correspondence N, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Correspondence O, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Correspondence P, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Q, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Correspondence R, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Correspondence S, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Correspondence S, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Correspondence T, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Correspondence U, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Correspondence V, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Correspondence W, 1995-2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Correspondence X/Y, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Z, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Constitutions, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Article XX and XXI, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO Conventions - Special Convention, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO Conference for Union Pension Fund Trustees, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO Conference - Diversity (Speech by Mazur), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Lawyers Coordinating Committee Colloquium, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO ACTPN, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Advisory Committee for Trade Policy (ACTPN), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO ACTPN, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiations (ACTPN), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO ACTPN, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Scope and Contents
  December 4, 1997
- AFL-CIO Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiation, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO American Center for Labor Solidarity, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA) Convention Speech, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Campaign for Global Fairness, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO COPE (Committee on Political Education), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Economic Policy Council, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Health Care, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Immigration Policy, Special Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO IUD Executive Committee, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO IUD - Executive Council, 20th Constitutional Convention, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO International Affairs Department, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO International Affairs Committee, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO - Israel Trip, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO Legislative and Political, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO Legislative and Political Communication Guide - GOP Attacks, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Organizing Fund, Conference, Summer, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO Los Angeles Orange County Organizing Committee, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO International Organizing and Solidarity Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO - Presidents - Sweeney, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Social Security Company, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Stop Sweatshops Campaign (Citizens Committee Against Sweatshops), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Trade Subcommittee, 1995-1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Trade-Labor Advisory Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Union Label and Service Trade Department, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Working Women's Department, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- ACTPN, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Advisory Committee on Trade Policy Negotiation (ACTPN), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Bank Opening NJ, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Bank First Anniversary Reception, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Bank - Opening, Washington, D.C., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Bank, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Trust Company of California, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- American Center for Labor Solidarity, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- AFT (American Federation of Textiles), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- AFT (American Federation of Teachers) - Convention - Videotaped Remarks, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- American Labor Museum (Botto House), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- American Prospect Reception, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Bahr, Morty, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Biddeford Textile Company, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Canadian Conference, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Canadian Staff Meeting, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Canadian Suit Imports - Talking Points with Mickey Kantor, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Cannon Mills Organizing Campaign, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Carribbean Basin Institute (CBI), 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Central America, Meeting Remarks, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Central America - Visitors, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Central American - U.S. Labor Ministers Meetings, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Child Care, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Child Labor March, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- China Resolution, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- China Trade Rally, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Chinatown Rally, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Clinton, Hillary Talking Points, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Clothing Manufacturers of America (CMA), 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Consumer Assembly, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Corzine, Jon, Endorsement Speech, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Costume Bundles - Campaign on Broadway, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Costume Makers Justice Campaign (NYC), 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Dodds, Malcolm Memorial, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Dominican Republican - Cap and Gown Tour, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Donahue, Tom - Foreign Affairs Response, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Donahue, Tom, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Donahue, Tom - Remarks by, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Dubrow, Evelyn - Retirement Reception, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- FITTVCC, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Fast Track, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Fasanella, Ralph, Memorial Service, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Finley Murray Memorial Service, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Fisher, Joe, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Friedman, Jesse, Eulogy for, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Garment Center (NYC) Press Conference, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC) Remarks, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- GIDC Remarks, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Gephardt, Representative Richard, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Globalization - Council for the United States and Italy, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Globalization - State of the World Forum, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Globalization, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Guatemala - Meeting with Ambassador - talking points, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Guess, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Hillman Foundation Awards, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Hoffman, Sol, Eulogy for, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Hoffman, Sol, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Immigration - National Immigration Forum, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Immigration Forum, AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Immigration - Ellis Island Rally, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  May 1997
- Immigration - Ellis Island Institution, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  August 1997
- Immigration - Legislation, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Immigration - New American Citizens, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Israeli Bonds, Philadelphia, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Italian American Labor Council, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Italian American Labor Council (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Italian American Labor Council, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Italian American Labor Council, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Japan, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Martin Luther King Jr., Events, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Kirkland, Lane, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA) (AFL-CIO), 2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Labor - Management Councils - Mid-Atlantic Region, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Levi Strauss Negotiation, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Levine, Randy, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Local 23-25, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Lobby Day, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Lower Fast Side Tenement Museum, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Malden Mills, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Mazur's Farewell Speech, UNITE Presidency, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Mt. Sinai - Selikoff Center for Occupational and Environmental Medicine, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- National Committee for Labor Israel - Lancry Reception, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- National Committee for Labor Israel (NCLI) - Ambassador Avital Reception, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- National Committee for Labor Israel - Israel and Labor 50 years Remarks by Jay Mazur, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- National Cooperative Business Association (NCBA) - Housing Award Remarks, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- National Council of Senior Citizens Convention, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- National Labor Committee, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- New Jersey Procurement Legislation, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- NYC Central Labor Council: Ordinary People, Extraordinary Lives, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- New York City Central Labor Council Rally, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- NYC Mobilization Rally, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- New York Skirt and Sportswear Convention, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Oath of Office (UNITE Canada), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Outerwear Negotiations, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Persian Funds, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 26)